Hey, guys...
Wait,
let me tell them.
Sure.
Joey's going to be
a celebrity guest
on a game show.
Oh.
Really? Which one?
Fish. Seaweed.
A sunken ship.
Things you find
in the ocean.
You're going to be
on Pyramid!
Oh, it was our favorite
game show ever.
Except for Match Game.
Or Win, Lose or Draw.
What did I marry into?
Well, do you guys want
to come down tomorrow
and watch me
tape the show?
Oh, we can't.
We're throwing Phoebe
a bachelorette party.
Yeah, sorry, boys.
This ride's closing.
Well, and Chandler
and I have
this stupid
college alumni thing.
I can't believe you get
to meet Donny Osmond.
Seriously?
Yuh-huh!
Ross and I always wanted
to be Donny and Marie.
You guys just keep getting
cooler and cooler.
We used to perform for
our family and friends.
Oh, God, that's right.
I blocked that out.
♪ I'm a little bit country ♪
♪ And I'm a little bit
rock and roll. ♪
I'm leaving you.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
It's so weird to see
all these people again.
Oh, my God, look,
there's Jeffrey Klarik.
Who?
He was roommates
with John Rosoff?
He went out with
Andrea Tamborino?
She dumped him
for Michael Skloff?
Did I go to
this school?
Hey, there's
Missy Goldberg.
You got
to remember her.
Sure. Nice.
Dude, you're married
to my sister.
You're right.
By saying "nice,"
I'm virtually licking her.
Hey, I hear she's
single again.
Think I should
ask her out?
Are you asking
permission to
break the pact?
Yes, please.
Hey.
Hey, check out the
fliers for the band.
I made them on a Macintosh
in the computer room.
Awesome.
The name really stands out.
Thanks to a little something
called Helvetica Bold 24 point.
Man, we're going to rock
that Asian Student Union!
Hey, guys.
Hey, Missy.
You know, our band is
playing on Friday.
Yeah, yeah, you should come
check us out.
We're called "Way/No Way."
No way.
Way!
Great. I'll
be there.
Fresh.
Boss.
Mint.
She's gone.
I know it.
You know, I'm totally
going to ask her out.
Dude, I was going
to ask her out.
I said it first, bro.
Oh, I thought it first, Holmes.
Look, if you think...
Wait, wait.
What are we doing?
What we have is
too important
to mess it up
over some girl.
I mean, we can get laid
anytime we want.
Totally.
I had sex in high school.
Me, too.
I'm good at it.
All right, I say we make a pact.
Neither of us will go out
with Missy Goldberg.
You got it.
All right, so that's
Missy Goldberg, Phoebe Cates
and Molly Ringwald who neither
of us can go out with.
Those are the pacts.
Oh, and Sheena Easton.
But we probably couldn't
get her anyway.
Huh! Huh! Maybe not you.
Well, I officially
give you permission
to break the pact.
Thank you.
All right, here I go.
Now, remember how scary
it used to be
going up to girls in college?
Your hands are shaking.
I know, and I can't
stop sweating.
...four, three, applause!
( cheering )
Yeah!
Welcome.
It is Soap Opera Week
here on Pyramid.
Let's meet our contestants.
First, Gene Lester is
a database specialist.
He's going to be playing
with Days of Our Lives star,
Joey Tribianni!
( applause and cheers )
And over here,
we have Henrietta Cherry...
Listen, I know
it can be intimidating
for regular people
to be around celebrities,
but relax, I'm just like you,
only better-looking
and richer.
...she'll be playing
with star
of General Hospital,
Leslie Charleson...
( applause )
Welcome, everybody.
Good luck to all of you.
Let's play Pyramid.
All right.
Now, we flipped
a coin before the show.
Gene, you won the toss,
so you're going to start.
Which category would you like?
I'll take
"You Crossed the Line."
Joey, describe for Gene
these things that have lines.
Give me 20 seconds
on the clock, please.
Ready. Go.
Uh, okay, it's a store
like a supermarket...
( buzzer )
Oh, I see what I did there.
Okay, okay.
I'm writing in my...
Diary?
No, more like a notebook--
( buzzer )
Damn it!
Um... oh, if I'm
building a house,
the plan isn't called
a shmooprint...
( buzzer )
I can't do that either?
Oh, in high school,
I once had sex with a girl
right in the middle of the...
Cafeteria.
Yeah, but that's not
what they're looking for.
( buzzer )
Oh!
Thank you so much
for this.
Aw... you like it?
Oh, my God, it's
all so elegant.
When's the dirty
stuff starting?
What?
You know, the strippers
and the guys dancing
and, you know,
pee-pees flying about.
Oh!
Pheebs, I... There isn't
going to be any "flying about."
We actually thought
we were a little too mature
for stuff like that.
Oh, okay.
I see what you're
doing. That's fine.
This is all there is.
Just tea. Okay.
Mmm... Raunchy.
It's okay.
Seriously, Pheebs,
it's not going to be
that kind of a party.
Really?
So th-this is...
this is my big send-off
into married life?
Rachel, this is the only
bachelorette party
I'm ever going to have.
I've, I've got a big wad
of ones in my purse.
Really? I mean really?
It's just tea?
No!
Phoebe, of course there's more.
Okay.
I mean, let me just
go talk to Monica
and get an ETA on the pee-pees.
Gene, I must remind you,
you need all six of these
to stay in the game, all right?
Describe for Joey things
you find in your refrigerator.
They might as well
just give us the points.
( chuckles )
Give me 20 seconds
on the clock.
Ready. Go.
You put this in your coffee.
A spoon! Your hands! Your face!
It's white.
Paper! Snow! A ghost!
It's heavier than milk.
A rock. A dog. The Earth.
Pass. You put this
on a sandwich.
Salami. Anchovies. Jam.
It's white.
Paper! Snow! A ghost!
It's made from eggs.
Chickens!
Pass!
Oh...
You put it on a hamburger.
Ketchup!
Yes.
Relish!
Stop!
( buzzer )
Oh.
Oh, time's up.
Joey, you were almost
on a roll there.
Gene, you're going
to have a chance
to go to the Winner's Circle
in the second half,
but right now, Henrietta,
you are going
to the Winner's Circle
to try your luck for $10,000
right after this.
Don't go away.
And we're out.
Oh, so we didn't win.
But it's fun to play
the game, right?
Hey, I got a kid
starting college.
I have to get surgery
on my knee.
You just lost me ten grand.
Oh, wow.
I'm so sorry.
Okay, I promise,
we'll do better next time.
Well, I will, because
I won't be playing with you.
You know, some of those
were pretty hard.
Like, why would there be
a ghost in my fridge?
Yeah.
So, Saturday night?
I'd love to.
Great.
So how come it took you
so long to ask me out?
Oh, well, uh, this is
going to sound kind
of silly, but...
Do you remember
my roommate Chandler Bing?
Sure. He was in your "band."
It's been 16 years,
but the air quotes still hurt.
Sorry.
That's okay.
Anyway, well, he and I both
really liked you a lot, um,
but we didn't want anything
to jeopardize your friendship,
so we kind of made a pact
that neither of us
could ask you out.
Really?
Yeah. Why?
Well, Chandler and I
used to make out... a lot.
You did?
Yeah. We'd go to the
science lab after hours.
And on my turf?!
Hey, where is this guy?
It's been over an hour.
Well, he's coming from Jersey.
He said he would get here
as fast as he could.
( pounding on door )
Who is it?
It's the police.
The police!
Oh!
That's right,
it's Officer Goodbody.
What's the matter, Officer,
has someone been bad?
( coughing )
Whoo, that's a lot of stairs.
Hoo, boy.
You should warn people
there's no elevator.
( groaning ):
Whoa, oh...
I should not have
had that Mexican
food for lunch.
Are-are you gonna be okay,
Officer, uh...
Goodbody.
If you say so.
So, where's
the young lady
who I am supposed to take...
downtown?
Oh, God.
All right,
somebody show me
where to plug in my box,
and we'll get this party
started.
Wah!
Where? All right.
Rachel?
Yeah?
Um,
are you kidding?
All right, look,
we did not know that
you wanted a stripper,
so we went
to the phone book,
and we got the first name
we could find.
How old's your phone book?!
Oh, my God, this man
is gonna get naked
in my apartment.
Oh, no, I don't want to see
him take his clothes off.
Are you talking
about me?
Oh, no.
I mean, obviously, we want to
see you take your clothes off...
you big piece of eye candy.
Okay, okay, ladies,
can I have your
attention, please?
Oh, yeah.
Did someone call
for the long arm of the law?
I should warn you,
I have a concealed weapon.
I hope you're familiar
with this state's...
penal code.
Okay, okay,
enough teasin'.
Now for some pleasin'.
( Soft Cell's "Tainted Love"
playing )
♪ Sometimes I feel
I've got to ♪
♪ Run away, I've got to ♪
♪ Get away from ♪
♪ The pain you drive
into the heart of me ♪
♪ The love we share ♪
♪ Seems to go no... ♪
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
She cringed!
This is how I look
when I'm turned on.
You were talking
about me before.
Look, I don't need this.
I'm out of here.
Where's my hat?
Look, I've been in this
business for a long time.
Shocking.
Now if you'll just
pay me my $300,
I'll be on my way.
$300? Are you kidding?
No, that's okay,
let me just get
my checkbook.
No, you're not gonna pay him--
he didn't do anything.
Didn't do anything?
I took a bus
all the way from Hoboken.
I climbed, I don't know,
like, a billion stairs.
And it's not like I can
take them two at a time.
I don't care, we're not
paying you $300 for this.
Well, look, it's not my fault
if you're too uptight
to appreciate the male form
in all its glory.
Oh, yeah, okay, I'm uptight.
Yeah, that's why I
don't want to watch
a middle-aged guy
dance around in what
I can only assume is a
child's Halloween costume.
I may have borrowed this
from my nephew...
but let me assure you,
what's underneath is all man.
I'm sorry, did you say
"all man" or "old man"?
( groans ):
Oh... you're mean.
Uh, look, Officer, uh, sir...
Damn it! Oh...
( groans )
Big surprise: the hunk
of beef has feelings.
Okay, Henrietta,
you picked
"Jack and Jill
Went Up the Hill."
My friend Rachel
has a kid.
I totally know
nursery rhymes.
Joey, describe
these things
associated with
the United States Congress.
Give me 20 seconds
on the clock, please.
Ready... go.
Uh... uh...
Pass.
Okay, the little thing
that hangs down
in the back of your throat.
A uvula.
Oh. Then pass.
( buzzer)
( groans ):
Oh!
OSMOND:
Okay.
Henrietta, you didn't get
all the points
you needed, so that means, Gene,
you are going to
the Winner's Circle
to try for $10,000,
and you're gonna be going there
with Joey Tribbiani!
You made out with
Missy Goldberg?
How could you do that
after you promised me?
Excuse me.
That didn't make us
sound gay at all.
You broke the pact!
Ross, that was
16 years ago.
That doesn't matter.
We're talking about
the foundation of
our friendship.
I believe the foundation
of our friendship
was unfortunate hair.
All right, look,
if we're really gonna do this,
it's not like you never
broke one of the pacts.
I didn't.
( chuckles ):
Oh, really?
No.
No!
Adrienne Turner!
Yes?
Hey, Adrienne.
Hi, Adrienne.
I never did anything
with Adrienne Turner.
Oh, please-- and you knew
how much I liked her.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Really? Remember that
big party freshman year,
a week before
Christmas vacation?
I do. You had some visitors.
I can't believe we're
at a real college party.
I have to pee so bad.
This is so awesome.
College guys are so cute.
Hey, you've got
a boyfriend.
I know.
But if some guy who
looks like Corey Haim
wants to kiss me tonight,
I am so gonna let him.
Oh, hey, look.
There's Chandler.
You know, that
stupid friend of Ross's
who said I was fat.
You know, I've already
lost four pounds.
You can so totally tell.
I know!
Well, let's see, maybe
he knows where Ross is.
Hey, how's it going?
Aren't you...
Yeah, Rachel.
And this is
Ross's sister Monica.
We met at Thanksgiving.
( chuckles ):
Right. So, how you doing?
Bitchin'.
Hi, Monica.
Hi, Chandler.
It's really nice
to see you.
Not. ( snickers )
Okay.
I'll see if I
can find Ross.
Okay.
Oh, my God, Rach,
beanbag chairs.
Oh.
Do not let me sit
in one of those.
We'll be here for days.
Listen, Adrienne,
you can't tell Chandler
about this.
Oh, believe me, Ross,
I won't be telling
anybody about this.
Cool.
I didn't know you
knew about that.
Well, I did, and it hurt.
That's when I wrote the song,
"Betrayal in the Common Room."
( sighs )
Man, I... I'm sorry.
Look... it was
a long time ago.
So, uh...
I made out with Adrienne,
and you made out with Missy.
Well, I guess we're even.
Mm-hmm.
We are even, right?
( sighs )
Just one more thing.
I was so pissed at you
that night
that I wanted
to get back at you,
so I thought,
who does Ross like
more than anybody?
What did you do to my mom?
Not her.
( dance music playing )
♪ Talk about, talk about ♪
♪ Talk about movin' ♪
♪ Gotta move on ♪
I am so drunk.
That's weird-- I've had
the same number of beers as you,
and I don't feel
anything at all.
So, you girls
having fun?
For your information,
assmunch...
...I've lost four pounds.
Maybe even five,
with all the dancing.
Did somebody order a pizza?
Oh, that's me!
I am so not gonna do good
on my SATs tomorrow.
Well, maybe you could go
to school here next year,
and we could
totally hang out.
Oh, yeah, there's a plan.
Why don't I just start
taking my smart pills now.
Well, maybe you could get in
on a beauty scholarship.
( laughs ):
What a line.
So, where are you
applying to?
Um, well, you know, I think
it's kind of really important
that I go somewhere
where there's sun,
so I'm sort of...
Hey!
I'm in college,
and I'm in a band.
Yeah, okay.
♪ Gotta move on... ♪
What's the matter?
You never saw a 50 year-old
stripper cry before?
You know, it's fine.
We'll pay you.
No, no,
you're right.
Who am I kidding?
I should've hung up that
break-away jock strap years ago.
What am I gonna do?
I mean, this has been
my life for 32 years.
Taking my clothes off in front
of people is all I know.
Well, wait, no,
there's got to be
something else
that you can do.
I mean, what skills
do you have?
I don't know.
I can make my pecs dance.
I can pick up a dollar
bill with my butt cheeks.
I can go to that special
place inside me
where I feel no shame.
So maybe something in an office?
Or you could, you
could teach stripping.
You know, share
your gift.
Pass the torch.
You know, actually
that's not a bad idea.
I could do it
out of my apartment.
I don't think my mom would mind.
All right,
there you go.
Okay, you think you're
going to be okay?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
This is so weird.
You never know when it's
gonna be your last dance.
And I didn't even get
a chance to finish it.
Finish it.
What?
Your last dance--
do it for us.
Really?
Yeah. Yeah.
He deserves to do the thing
he loves one last time.
Okay. All right.
Get ready, ladies.
Okay.
( upbeat dance music plays )
( whooping )
( screaming )
Oh, this is so hot!
Oh, no, no,
don't stop.
( panting )
Have to.
Oh.
Well, welcome to
the Winner's Circle.
Joey, Gene,
you guys ready?
Yeah.
Sure.
Okay. Give me
60 seconds
on the clock, please.
Ready. Go.
Oak, maple, elm, birch.
I dunno...
Types of trees.
( bell rings )
Uh... Buenos dias.
Enchilada. Por favor.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I don't know any Spanish words.
( bell rings )
Wow.
A match. A candle.
Things that go "tsss"
when you put them out.
A torch. A bonfire.
Uh... Your pee.
Things that burn!
"I'd like to go for a walk."
"Scratch my belly."
Dude, dude, I think
you're losing it.
"I have fur."
"I like to bark."
Oh, oh, oh. What a dog says.
Peppero...
Pizza toppings! Next!
Cindy Crawford. Christie
Brinkley. Heidi Klum.
Claudia Schiffer.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Christy Turlington.
Uh, Kate Moss.
Girls Chandler could never get?
( buzzer )
Supermodels.
Where?
Hey. Where's Rachel?
She and Phoebe took
the stripper to the hospital.
Did you know Chandler
kissed Rachel?
What? When, when was this?.
1987.
The weekend you guys
visited me at school.
Oh, my God. That's wild.
Yeah, but it was like
a million years ago,
so it doesn't matter.
Well, it matters to me.
Why?
Because the night
you kissed Rachel
was the night
I kissed Rachel
for the very first time.
You kissed her
that night, too?
Two guys in one night?
Oh, I thought
she became a slut
after she got her nose fixed.
Seriously,
where did this happen?
Okay, after you told me she
was passed out in our room,
I went in there to make
sure she was all right.
She was lying on my bed, all
buried in people's coats.
Well, I-I went to kiss
her on the forehead,
you know, but it was so dark
I accidentally got her lips.
I started to pull away,
but then I felt her
start to kiss me back.
It was only for
a second, but...
it was amazing
and now, now I find out
that you kissed her first.
Wait-- what bed
did you say she was on?
Mine.
I'm pretty sure
I put her on my bed.
No, she was
definitely on my bed.
Why would I kiss a girl
and then put her on your bed?
Well, then, who
was on my bed?
Oh! Oh! Oh!
No! No, no!
Yes!
You were under
the pile of coats?
I was the pile of coats.
Oh, my God!
You were
my mystery midnight kisser?!
my first kiss with Rachel?!
You were my first kiss ever?!
What did I
marry into?!
( dance music playing )
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Aw, crap.